Because we're lazy engineers, we're
going to take something that works,
우리는 게으른 엔지니어이기 때문에 작동하는 무언가를 취하고
a logistic classifier and do the minimal
amount of change to make it non-linear.
로지스틱 분류기를 사용하여 최소한의 변화만으로 비선형으로 만듭니다.
We're going to construct our new
function in the simplest way that we can
우리는 우리가 생각할 수있는 가장 간단한 방법으로 새로운 기능을
think of.
구성 할 것입니다.
Instead of having a single matrix
multiplier as our classifier,
우리의 분류 자로 하나의 행렬 곱셈을하는 대신,
we're going to insert
a RELU right in the middle.
중간에 RELU를 삽입 할 것입니다.
We now have two matrices.
우리는 이제 두 개의 행렬을가집니다.
One going from the inputs to the RELUs,
and
하나는 입력에서 RELUs로 가고
another one connecting
the RELUs to the classifier.
다른 하나는 RELUs를 분류 자로 연결합니다.
We've solved two of our problems.
우리는 두 가지 문제를 해결했습니다.
Our function in now nonlinear thanks
to the RELU in the middle, and
중간에 RELU 덕분에 우리의 기능은 비선형 적으로 작동합니다
we now have a new knob that we can tune,
this number H which
우리는 지금 우리가 조정할 수있는 새로운 손잡이를 가지고 있습니다.
corresponds to the number of RELU
units that we have in the classifier.
이 숫자 H는 분류기에있는 RELU 유닛의 수와 같습니다.
We can make it as big as we want.
우리는 우리가 원하는만큼 크게 만들 수 있습니다.
Congratulations, you've built
your first neural network.
첫 번째 신경망을 구축 한 것을 축하드립니다.
You might ask, wait a minute,
where's my neuron?
잠깐, 내 신경은 어디 있니?
In the past, when talking about neural
networks, I remember seeing diagrams
과거에는 신경에 ​​대해 이야기 할 때 네트워크에서
with dendrites, axons, activation
functions, brains, neuroscience.
수상 돌기, 축삭, 활성화 기능, 두뇌, 신경 과학이있는 다이어그램을 보았던 것을 기억합니다.
Where is all that?
그게 다 어디 갔지?